getlucky.com 2017-10-14

# Get Lucky - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
Co-Gaming Limited Privacy Policy  
Last Updated 6th January 2016

**Introduction**

Co-Gaming Limited wants visitors to its Website to know that we are just as concerned as you are about the privacy of any personal information that you may choose to provide us. Your privacy is important to you and to us so we will protect the information you share with us. To protect your privacy, Co-Gaming Limited follows different principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection.

This privacy policy, together with our general [terms and conditions](https://www.getlucky.com/terms/) describes how Co-Gaming Limited collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Website http://www.getlucky.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at support (at) getlucky.com.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We collect the following personal information from you:

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletters or marketing emails by “switching off” the options in the ‘Newsletter Settings’ found in the area ‘My Account’ on our Website or you can contact us at support (at) getlucky.com.

**Facebook Connect or Open ID**  
You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Website to your profile page to share with others within your network.

**Chat**  
We use a chat feature to assist you with all your questions and concerns regarding our products and services. Our chat service requires you to insert name, username and email so that our customer care agents can find your account in the back office. If our chat feature is offline we will collect your name and email address so that we may reply to your request.

**Information Sharing**  
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.  
We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as but not limited to card processing, payments, identity verification and customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information:

**Cookies**  
We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

**Third Party Cookies**  
The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

**Widgets**  
Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, or deactivate it by making the change on our Website in the area ‘My Account’ or by emailing our Customer Support at support (at) getlucky.com.

**Links to Other Websites**  
Our Site includes links to other Websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Co-Gaming Limited. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Website you visit.

**Surveys or Contests**  
From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code).

**Testimonials**  
We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our website which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. To request removal of your personal information from Testimonials or comments please contact us at support (at) getlucky.com.

**Data Retention**  
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support (at) getlucky.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. The transmission of all information collected on our Site is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  
Co-Gaming Limited complies with Payment Card Industry (PCI) Data Security Standards.

**Notification of Privacy Policy Changes**  
We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on our Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or want to contact us regarding how we handle your data, please send an email to support (at) getlucky.com or write to us at:

Co-Gaming Limited  
Forth Mansions,  
Ground Floor & 1st Floor  
Ta’ Xbiex Sea Front,  
Ta’ Xbiex, XBX 1027  
Malta
